

### **Details**

267-318-8206 timuism@me.com

#### Links

My Website

Linked In

## **Skills**

HTML & CSS

JavaScript, React, Vue, jQuery Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, SCSS Node/NPM, Yarn, Webpack Git

PHP, Wordpress, Laravel, MySQL Photoshop & Illustrator

Sketch, Figma

### **Profile**

Web Developer & UI Designer with experience in building both small websites and large web applications. Specializes in front-end development but has experience in back-end development, information technology, technical support, customer service, and client relations.

# **Employment History**

Web Developer, Blue Ocean Ideas, Towson, MD

MAY 2017 - PRESENT

- Collaborate with in-house designers to build functional user interfaces
- Write clean, efficient, and readable code within a large codebase
- Build and manage style guides & design systems
- Provide technical and developmental support for multiple clients

## Freelance Web Developer, Philadelphia, PA

SEPTEMBER 2008 - PRESENT

- Design & Build websites for small businesses
- · Serve as consultant for site creation and digital marketing
- · Helped small businesses move existing services online
- Design Logos, Posters, Graphics for artists and musicians

### Apple Technician, Apple Inc, Towson, MD

NOVEMBER 2009 - APRIL 2019

- Repaired Macs & iPhone devices as an Apple Certified Macintosh Technician
- Led training for prospective technicians and new employees
- Consistently surpassed metrics for customers assisted & promoters created

## **Education**

Web Design & Interactive Media, Art Institute of Philadelphia

OCTOBER 2006 - MARCH 2010

### References

George Puthukkeril from Procurated

georigin@gmail.com | 410-424-9683

Jon Franklin from Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory j.franklinjr@me.com | 443-324-8655

**April Cook from April Cook Salon** 

acook040389@gmail.com | 443-314-3265